When it comes to producing amazing
content,
[snaps fingers] some people think that
you need to have a studio, sound engineer,
chief fluffer, just in case it's
looking small,
and then a head of discombobulation.
But in reality,
you don't need six expensive cameras,
two directional
microphones. All of this is just overkill.
What you need is to understand hooks,
setups, how to film properly with your
iPhone, where the eye level should be,
and how to get good quality audio.
Then after that,
you've just got to keep making hundreds of
pieces of content until
you get good enough at it
that it can run and support your business.
Good news for you is I have a short form
content mastery course that you can access
right now. All you need to do
is comment the word "content"
and I'll send you all
the information to it.